

Driving innovation at the intersection of finance and technology. Delivering exceptional results through analytical expertise, strategic thinking, and client-focused solutions

⊕ tylerbustard.ca · 🖾 tbustard@unb.ca · 🗞 +1 (613) 985-1223 · ⑨ Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Education



Bachelor of Business Administration - Finance Major

2020

University of New Brunswick

Saint John, New Brunswick

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Case Competitions: 1st Place (CIBC), 3rd Place (TD), RBC and SLC participant
- $\bullet \ \text{Analyst and Portfolio Manager} \text{University of New Brunswick Student Investment Fund} \\$
- UNB Finance Club, RBC Student Ambassador, Accredited Co-op Program
- Recipient of 5 Scholarship and Alumni Awards for academic merit and leadership skills, Total \$47,500

Professional Experience



Portfolio Assistant

2022 - 2023

BMO Private Wealth

- Advised two Investment Counsellors managing portfolios over \$100M and cut preparation time by 12%
- Bolstered client communications, boosting response rates by 9% heightening client satisfaction and retention

Portfolio Management Client Relations Financial Analysis Excel



2021 - 2022

TD Canada Trust

- $\bullet \ \, \text{Cultivated strong client relationships by assessing individual financial needs, resulting in an 11\% increase in sales } \\$
- \bullet Exceeded sales targets, achieving a top 15% performance ranking within the district

Financial Planning Sales Client Advisory Product Knowledge



Banking Advisor

2020 - 2021

Royal Bank of Canada

Kingston Ontari

- Strengthened client relationships by advising on personalized solutions, increased repeat transactions by 13%
- Excelled in needs-based advising, boosting adoption of core products like GICs, mutual funds, and TFSAs by 8%

Banking Products Financial Advisory Client Relationship Management Digital Banking

